John and Susan Edwards Harvith Interview Collection
John and Susan Edwards Harvith Interview Collection
- Interviews
  - Jane Wyatt, part 3, 07/24/1998; harvith_int_124; interview with actress Jane Wyatt; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Bud Yorkin, parts 1 and 2, 07/28/2000; harvith_int_125; interview with Bud Yorkin, film and television producer, director, writer and actor; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Bud Yorkin, part 3, 07/28/2000; harvith_int_126; interview with Bud Yorkin, film and television producer, director, writer and actor; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)